mdlottery.com 2017-12-28

# Maryland Lottery - About UsPrivacy Policy - www.mdlottery.com

### Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting Maryland State Government. We take data security and the privacy of your personal information very seriously. Maryland law mandates that State agencies shall not create personal records unless the need for the information is clearly established and that personal records shall be appropriate and relevant to the purposes for which they are collected, be accurate and current to the greatest extent possible, and not be obtained by fraudulent means. A State official who requests personal information from a person must notify the person regarding the purpose for which the information is collected; consequences to the person for refusing to provide the personal information; the person’s right to inspect, amend, or correct personal records; whether the information is generally available for public inspection; and whether the information is made available to or shared with other entities.

**Information Collected and Stored Automatically**

When you browse these web sites, read pages, or download information, certain information about your visit may be automatically gathered and stored. This information does not identify you personally and includes the following:

  * The internet domain (example: aol.com) and the IP address (the number automatically assigned to your computer when surfing the Web) from which you access our portal;
  * The type of browser and operating system used to access our site;
  * The date and time you access our site;
  * The pages you visit;
  * The address from which you linked to our website.

This information is used to make these web sites more useful to visitors, to learn about the number of visitors to our site, and the types of technology our visitors use. We do not track or record identifying information about individuals and their visits.

For information regarding the Maryland Lottery’s Privacy Policy regarding the www.mdlottery.com online network and regarding User Submissions, see the heading “Privacy” under “Terms and Conditions.”

**Cookies**

These web sites may use “temporary cookies” to track User navigation in order to make the User experience more useful. A temporary cookie is erased when the User closes the Web browser. The “temporary cookie”, also called a session cookie, is stored in temporary memory in the form of a text file on your computer, and is erased after the browser session is ended. No identifying User information is collected and stored on other computers anywhere. We store no personal information based on your visit to a www.mdlottery.com online network web site.

**E-mail**

If you [Contact Us](http://www.mdlottery.com/about-us/contact-us/), or if you send other email to the Maryland Lottery, we use the information you send us to respond to your inquiry, just as we do with written correspondence. E-mail correspondence, like mailed correspondence, may become a public record. As a public record, your correspondence could be disclosed to other parties upon their request, in accordance with Maryland’s public records law.

**General Privacy Policy**

It is our policy to preserve the privacy of personal records and to protect confidential or privileged information. Such information will be disclosed publicly only as required by the Public Information Act or as necessary and permissible to carry out official duties. Under State law, these policies do not apply to information gathered for certain specified purposes, such as the investigation of a possible violation of law. If you have any questions about these privacy policies, please e-mail them to [service.desk@maryland.gov](mailto:service.desk@maryland.gov) or, if specifically regarding the Lottery’s privacy policies, please [Contact Us](http://www.mdlottery.com/about-us/contact-us/). This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by the www.mdlottery.com online network [defined under “Disclaimer”]. ****

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Changes to our web sites may necessitate changes to the privacy policy. Timely notification of any changes will be posted here or, if specific to a site, on the Privacy Policy page for the appropriate web site. Please note other parts of the Site may also include Privacy terms.

Please refer to the [Department of Information Technology](http://doit.maryland.gov/Pages/default.aspx) website for additional details on information technology policies in Maryland. The State of Maryland is committed to providing you with websites over which you may securely and confidently transact business with the State.

_[Full List of Defined Terms](http://www.mdlottery.com/about-us/legal-definitions/)_
